<item name = "quote1">The best preparation for tomorrow is doing your best today.</item>
<item name = "quote2">The best and most beautiful things in the world cannot be seen or even touched - they must be felt with the heart.</item>
<item name = "quote3">What we think, we become.</item>
<item name = "quote4">Happiness is not something you postpone for the future; it is something you design for the present.</item>
<item name = "quote5">I can't change the direction of the wind, but I can adjust my sails to always reach my destination.</item>
<item name = "quote6">Start by doing what's necessary; then do what's possible; and suddenly you are doing the impossible.</item>
<item name = "quote7">Keep your face always toward the sunshine - and shadows will fall behind you.</item>
<item name = "quote8">Try to be a rainbow in someone's cloud.</item>
<item name = "quote9">Perfection is not attainable, but if we chase perfection we can catch excellence.</item>
<item name = "quote10">It is during our darkest moments that we must focus to see the light.</item>
<item name = "quote11">If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door.</item>
<item name = "quote12">Change your thoughts and you change your world.</item>
<item name = "quote13">Vitality shows in not only the ability to persist but the ability to start over.</item>
<item name = "quote14">Let us sacrifice our today so that our children can have a better tomorrow.</item>
<item name = "quote15">As we express our gratitude, we must never forget that the highest appreciation is not to utter words, but to live by them.</item>
<item name = "quote16">Nothing is impossible, the word itself says 'I'm possible'!</item>
<item name = "quote17">We know what we are, but know not what we may be.</item>
<item name = "quote18">My mission in life is not merely to survive, but to thrive; and to do so with some passion, some compassion, some humor, and some style.</item>
<item name = "quote19">Clouds come floating into my life, no longer to carry rain or usher storm, but to add color to my sunset sky.</item>
<item name = "quote20">Believe you can and you're halfway there.</item>
<item name = "quote21">Put your heart, mind, and soul into even your smallest acts. This is the secret of success.</item>
<item name = "quote22">Health is the greatest gift, contentment the greatest wealth, faithfulness the best relationship.</item>
<item name = "quote23">We must let go of the life we have planned, so as to accept the one that is waiting for us.</item>
<item name = "quote24">If you believe in yourself and have dedication and pride - and never quit, you'll be a winner. The price of victory is high but so are the rewards.</item>
<item name = "quote25">No act of kindness, no matter how small, is ever wasted.</item>
<item name = "quote26">Every story I create, creates me. I write to create myself.</item>
<item name = "quote27">There are two ways of spreading light: to be the candle or the mirror that reflects it.</item>
<item name = "quote28">The bird is powered by its own life and by its motivation.</item>
<item name = "quote29">Don't judge each day by the harvest you reap but by the seeds that you plant.</item>
<item name = "quote30">When the sun is shining I can do anything; no mountain is too high, no trouble too difficult to overcome.</item>
<item name = "quote31">Let your life lightly dance on the edges of Time like dew on the tip of a leaf.</item>
<item name = "quote32">Let your life lightly dance on the edges of Time like dew on the tip of a leaf.</item>
<item name = "quote33">A hero is someone who has given his or her life to something bigger than oneself.</item>
<item name = "quote34">Two roads diverged in a wood and I - I took the one less traveled by, and that has made all the difference.</item>
<item name = "quote35">Your big opportunity may be right where you are now.</item>
<item name = "quote36">You must do the things you think you cannot do.</item>
<item name = "quote37">What lies behind you and what lies in front of you, pales in comparison to what lies inside of you.</item>
<item name = "quote38">The measure of who we are is what we do with what we have.</item>
<item name = "quote39">The world is full of magical things patiently waiting for our wits to grow sharper.</item>
<item name = "quote40">Tears of joy are like the summer rain drops pierced by sunbeams.</item>
<item name = "quote41">Happiness is a butterfly, which when pursued, is always just beyond your grasp, but which, if you will sit down quietly, may alight upon you.</item>
<item name = "quote42">Happiness is the natural flower of duty.</item>
<item name = "quote43">I thank you God for this most amazing day, for the leaping greenly spirits of trees, and for the blue dream of sky and for everything which is natural, which is infinite, which is yes.</item>
<item name = "quote44">I will love the light for it shows me the way, yet I will endure the darkness because it shows me the stars.</item>
<item name = "quote45">No matter what people tell you, words and ideas can change the world.</item>
<item name = "quote46">Thousands of candles can be lighted from a single candle, and the life of the candle will not be shortened. Happiness never decreases by being shared.</item>
<item name = "quote47">Tomorrow is the most important thing in life. Comes into us at midnight very clean. It's perfect when it arrives and it puts itself in our hands. It hopes we've learned something from yesterday.</item>
<item name = "quote48">I hated every minute of training, but I said, 'Don't quit. Suffer now and live the rest of your life as a champion.'</item>
<item name = "quote49">Even if I knew that tomorrow the world would go to pieces, I would still plant my apple tree.</item>
<item name = "quote50">Let us remember: One book, one pen, one child, and one teacher can change the world.</item>
<item name = "quote51">Someone is sitting in the shade today because someone planted a tree a long time ago.</item>
<item name = "quote52">Follow your bliss and the universe will open doors where there were only walls.</item>
<item name = "quote53">Happiness resides not in possessions, and not in gold, happiness dwells in the soul.</item>
<item name = "quote54">Whoever is happy will make others happy too.</item>
<item name = "quote55">When you get into a tight place and everything goes against you, till it seems as though you could not hang on a minute longer, never give up then, for that is just the place and time that the tide will turn.</item>
<item name = "quote56">If we did all the things we are capable of, we would literally astound ourselves.</item>
<item name = "quote57">Thought is the wind, knowledge the sail, and mankind the vessel.</item>
<item name = "quote58">There is nothing impossible to him who will try.</item>
<item name = "quote59">The limits of the possible can only be defined by going beyond them into the impossible.</item>
<item name = "quote60">Keep all special thoughts and memories for lifetimes to come. Share these keepsakes with others to inspire hope and build from the past, which can bridge to the future.</item>
<item name = "quote61">Let us make our future now, and let us make our dreams tomorrow's reality.</item>
<item name = "quote62">The books that help you most are those which make you think that most. The hardest way of learning is that of easy reading; but a great book that comes from a great thinker is a ship of thought, deep freighted with truth and beauty.</item>
<item name = "quote63">Out of difficulties grow miracles.</item>
<item name = "quote64">Don't limit yourself. Many people limit themselves to what they think they can do. You can go as far as your mind lets you. What you believe, remember, you can achieve.</item>
<item name = "quote65">Everyone has inside of him a piece of good news. The good news is that you don't know how great you can be! How much you can love! What you can accomplish! And what your potential is!</item>
<item name = "quote66">God always gives His best to those who leave the choice with him.</item>
<item name = "quote67">The things that we love tell us what we are.</item>
<item name = "quote68">How wonderful it is that nobody need wait a single moment before starting to improve the world.</item>
<item name = "quote69">All you need is the plan, the road map, and the courage to press on to your destination.</item>
<item name = "quote70">If you always put limit on everything you do, physical or anything else. It will spread into your work and into your life. There are no limits. There are only plateaus, and you must not stay there, you must go beyond them.</item>
<item name = "quote71">Give light, and the darkness will disappear of itself.</item>
<item name = "quote72">Turn your face to the sun and the shadows fall behind you.</item>
<item name = "quote73">Throw your dreams into space like a kite, and you do not know what it will bring back, a new life, a new friend, a new love, a new country.</item>
<item name = "quote74">Look within. Within is the fountain of good, and it will ever bubble up, if thou wilt ever dig.</item>
<item name = "quote75">From what we get, we can make a living; what we give, however, makes a life.</item>
<item name = "quote76">Find out who you are and be that person. That's what your soul was put on this Earth to be. Find that truth, live that truth and everything else will come.</item>
<item name = "quote77">Everyone here has the sense that right now is one of those moments when we are influencing the future.</item>
<item name = "quote78">Ah, but a man's reach should exceed his grasp, Or what's a heaven for?</item>
<item name = "quote79">Live your beliefs and you can turn the world around.</item>
<item name = "quote80">Everything you want is out there waiting for you to ask. Everything you want also wants you. But you have to take action to get it.</item>
<item name = "quote81">What we need is more people who specialize in the impossible.</item>
<item name = "quote82">It is in your moments of decision that your destiny is shaped.</item>
<item name = "quote83">Enthusiasm moves the world.</item>
<item name = "quote84">What great thing would you attempt if you knew you could not fail?</item>
<item name = "quote85">Love is a fruit in season at all times, and within reach of every hand.</item>
<item name = "quote86">I believe that one defines oneself by reinvention. To not be like your parents. To not be like your friends. To be yourself. To cut yourself out of stone.</item>
<item name = "quote87">To the mind that is still, the whole universe surrenders.</item>
<item name = "quote88">It is always the simple that produces the marvelous.</item>
<item name = "quote89">Joy descends gently upon us like the evening dew, and does not patter down like a hailstorm.</item>
<item name = "quote90">I believe every human has a finite number of heartbeats. I don't intend to waste any of mine.</item>
<item name = "quote91">It is never too late to be what you might have been.</item>
<item name = "quote92">We have it in our power to begin the world over again.</item>
<item name = "quote93">I believe in living today. Not in yesterday, nor in tomorrow.</item>
<item name = "quote94">And when I breathed, my breath was lightning.</item>
<item name = "quote95">We relish news of our heroes, forgetting that we are extraordinary to somebody too.</item>
<item name = "quote96">Man never made any material as resilient as the human spirit.</item>
<item name = "quote97">The glow of one warm thought is to me worth more than money.</item>
<item name = "quote98">Memories of our lives, of our works and our deeds will continue in others.</item>
<item name = "quote99">As people are walking all the time, in the same spot, a path appears.</item>
<item name = "quote100">It seems to me we can never give up longing and wishing while we are thoroughly alive. There are certain things we feel to be beautiful and good, and we must hunger after them.</item>
<item name = "quote101">Once we believe in ourselves, we can risk curiosity, wonder, spontaneous delight, or any experience that reveals the human spirit.</item>
<item name = "quote102">In oneself lies the whole world and if you know how to look and learn, the door is there and the key is in your hand. Nobody on earth can give you either the key or the door to open, except yourself.</item>
<item name = "quote103">Noble deeds that are concealed are most esteemed.</item>
<item name = "quote104">I have looked into your eyes with my eyes. I have put my heart near your heart.</item>
<item name = "quote105">Just don't give up trying to do what you really want to do. Where there is love and inspiration, I don't think you can go wrong.</item>
<item name = "quote106">If a man does not keep pace with his companions, perhaps it is because he hears a different drummer. Let him step to the music which he hears, however measured or far away.</item>
<item name = "quote107">You don't look out there for God, something in the sky, you look in you.</item>
<item name = "quote108">What we achieve inwardly will change outer reality.</item>
<item name = "quote109">Ideas shape the course of history.</item>
<item name = "quote110">With self-discipline most anything is possible.</item>
<item name = "quote111">Today is the only day. Yesterday is gone.</item>
<item name = "quote112">Love the moment and the energy of that moment will spread beyond all boundaries.</item>
<item name = "quote113">When we seek to discover the best in others, we somehow bring out the best in ourselves.</item>
<item name = "quote114">Without craftsmanship, inspiration is a mere reed shaken in the wind.</item>
<item name = "quote115">If I have seen further than others, it is by standing upon the shoulders of giants.</item>
<item name = "quote116">Let us dream of tomorrow where we can truly love from the soul, and know love as the ultimate truth at the heart of all creation.</item>
<item name = "quote117">I believe there's an inner power that makes winners or losers. And the winners are the ones who really listen to the truth of their hearts.</item>
<item name = "quote118">Love and desire are the spirit's wings to great deeds.</item>
<item name = "quote119">What makes the desert beautiful is that somewhere it hides a well.</item>
<item name = "quote120">Grace is the beauty of form under the influence of freedom.</item>
<item name = "quote121">My mind's my kingdom.</item>
<item name = "quote122">On the recollection of so many and great favours and blessings, I now, with a high sense of gratitude, presume to offer up my sincere thanks to the Almighty, the Creator and Preserver.</item>
<item name = "quote123">Let every dawn be to you as the beginning of life, and every setting sun be to you as its close.</item>
<item name = "quote124">The only journey is the one within.</item>
<item name = "quote125">You change your life by changing your heart.</item>
